<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Matsumoto Guide</string>
    <string name="sightseeing_category">Places</string>
    <string name="hotel_category">Hotels</string>
    <string name="museum_category">Museums</string>
    <string name="spa_category">Spa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_place">PlaceActivity</string>

    <string name="description">Description:</string>
    <string name="sample_description">Matsumoto Castle is one of the most complete and beautiful among Japan\'s original castles. Matsumoto Castle is unique for having both a secondary donjon and a turret adjoined to its main keep. The castle structures, in combination with their characteristic black wainscoting, give off an air of grandeur and poise.</string>
    <string name="where_it_is">Where it is?</string>

    <string name="sample_business_hours">9am – 9pm (doors close 8pm)</string>
    <string name="business_hours">Business hours:</string>
    <string name="sample_description_short">Matsumoto Castle (松本城, Matsumotojō) is one of the most complete and beautiful...</string>
    <string name="sample_name">Matsumot Castle</string>
    <string name="matsumoto_castle_name">Matsumoto Castle</string>
    <string name="matsumoto_castle_description">Matsumoto Castle is one of the most complete and
        beautiful among Japan\'s original castles.  Matsumoto Castle is unique for having both a secondary
        donjon and a turret adjoined to its main keep. The castle structures, in combination with
        their characteristic black wainscoting, give off an air of grandeur and poise.</string>
    <string name="matsumoto_castle_location">geo:36.238652,137.9667664,17z?q=Matsumoto Castle</string>
    <string name="nawate_name">Nawate Dori street</string>
    <string name="nawate_location">geo:36.2344467,137.9673989,17z?q=Nawate Dori</string>
    <string name="nawate_description">Located 5 minutes on foot from Matsumoto Castle and 10 min
        from Matsumoto Station, Nawate-dori is a shopping street that gives the feel of the city\'s
        history as a castle town. Lined with around 50 shops that vary from antique dealers and
        \'dagashi\' candy stores to stylish bakeries and designer boutiques, the frog-themed street
        makes a great place to stroll when seeing the castle.</string>
    <string name="nakamachi_name">Nakamachi District</string>
    <string name="nakamachi_location">geo:36.233834,137.9695607,17z?q=Nakamachi shopping street promotion association</string>
    <string name="nakamachi_description">During the Edo period (1603-1867) in Japan, Nakamachi
        Street was located in the center part of the castle town of Matsumoto City thus denoting its
        name: \“Naka\” – meaning in or center, and \“machi\” – meaning town. It was located on the old
        Zenkoji Kaido, a route connecting Zenkoji Temple to Nagoya and Kyoto and prospered as the
        main business district where wholesale dealers sold their goods (mainly sake brewers and
        kimono merchants). Many of the historical buildings found in Nakamachi used to function as
        storehouses. These buildings are called kura or dozo and some are more than a 100 years old.</string>
    <string name="agatanomori_name">Agatanomori Park</string>
    <string name="agatanomori_location">geo:36.2312858,137.9816192,17z?q=Agata Forest Park</string>
    <string name="agatonomori_description">Agatanomori Park in Matsumoto, Japan, is very much a
        local’s park. This forest park is a great place for families, couples, or people who want
        to relax in a peaceful and beautiful park. You’ll see animals, ponds, waterfalls, old
        buildings, and tall trees. You can also learn a bit about Matsumoto history by touring the
        historical Matsumoto High School building. Although it’s called a \“high school,\” back in
        the day the school curriculum was actually the equivalent to what we consider a college
        curriculum today, and served as the original location for Shinshu University."</string>
    <string name="richmond_hotel_name">Richmond Hotel Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="richmond_hotel_location">geo:36.2328025,137.9654184,17z?q=Richmond Hotel Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="richmond_hotel_description">Situated in Matsumoto, just a short walk from Matsumoto
        Railway Station, the hotel provides 4-star accommodation and free wireless internet. It also
        offers room service, a beauty centre and massage services. This hotel provides rooms with an
        en suite bathroom, air conditioning and a TV. Hot drinks can be made with the provided tea
        and coffee supplies. Richmond Hotel Matsumoto boasts convenient dining options, including
        Japanese dishes at Isemachi Yobanashi and Japanese food at Ohashi Café Gust. Matsumoto's
        popular attractions and landmarks are within close proximity to the hotel, with Matsumoto
        Castle only a short stroll away. Matsumoto Airport is a 25-minute drive away.</string>
    <string name="dormy_hotel_name">Dormy Inn Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="dormy_hotel_location">geo:36.2313822,137.9666229,17z?q=Dormy Inn Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="dormy_hotel_description">Dormy Inn Matsumoto provides a modern setting when in
        Matsumoto. It also features massage services, a sauna and free Wi-Fi. A 24-hour reception,
        luggage storage and a laundry service are just some of the convenient services at the hotel.
        The in-house spa and wellness centre provides a variety of treatments and a chance to relax.
        The modern rooms at Dormy Inn Matsumoto have air conditioning and offer slippers, tea and
        coffee making facilities and a refrigerator. They have an en suite bathroom with bathrobes,
        a hair dryer and a bathtub. Those staying at Dormy Inn Matsumoto can enjoy a unique dining
        experience at the in-house restaurant, conveniently situated for those who want to stay
        nearby when looking to sit down to a meal. The hotel is close to Matsumoto Railway Station,
        making it easy for guests to discover Matsumoto and its surrounding areas. Matsumoto Castle
        is within walking distance.</string>
    <string name="aceinn_hotel_name">Ace Inn Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="aceinn_hotel_location">geo:36.2300698,137.9636495,17z?q=Ace Inn Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="aceinn_hotel_description">Ace Inn Matsumoto offers 3-star accommodation in
        Matsumoto. It provides complimentary Wi-Fi, free bicycle rental and off-site parking. Ace
        Inn features 158 air conditioned rooms equipped with all the necessities to ensure a
        comfortable stay. After settling in to their room, guests can explore the local area with
        use of Matsumoto Railway Station, which is within a five-minute walk of the hotel. Those
        staying at the property can wake up to a satisfying breakfast prepared every morning, before
        heading out from Ace Inn Matsumoto to discover the surrounding area. Ace Inn is surrounded
        by the area\'s well-known sightseeing attractions, including Matsumoto Castle, which is a
        short walk away. The Kaichi School Museum is in close proximity to the property.</string>
    <string name="premier_hotel_name">Premier Hotel Cabin Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="premier_hotel_location">geo:36.2306073,137.9639813,17z?q=Premier Hotel Cabin Matsumoto</string>
    <string name="premier_hotel_description">Premier Hotel Cabin Matsumoto is situated in Matsumoto
        and is close to the area\'s tourist attractions. It offers complimentary Wi-Fi, massage
        services and laundry facilities. The hotel has 106 rooms and has been recently refurbished.
        Welcoming and professional team members are available 24 hours a day. The air conditioned
        rooms at Premier Hotel Cabin Matsumoto are well-appointed. Each has a bathroom that has a
        hair dryer and slippers. Serving Japanese dishes, the on-site restaurant features an
        air-conditioned dining room along with an outdoor terrace. There is also a variety of
        breakfast options to choose from every day. Premier Hotel Cabin Matsumoto is within walking
        distance of Matsumoto Castle. The hotel's multilingual staff are available to ensure that
        every traveller has a comfortable stay.</string>
    <string name="oiwakeya_name">Oiwakeya Ryokan</string>
    <string name="oiwakeya_location">geo:36.2454033,137.9961833,17z?q=Oiwakeya</string>
    <string name="oiwakeya_description">Beautiful Ryokan in a quiet residential area of Matsumoto.
        The service is excellent, a real Japanese experience. The Ryokan is nicely decorated and
        there are also Koi fish inside! The room is big with Tatami floor. They have both public and
        private Onsen, the private is relaxing with external and internal pool. Had a full Kaiseki
        Dinner, that was good but not the best I had in Japan. The Ryokan is a bit far from the train
        station, about 10 minutes by cab.</string>
    <string name="biwanoyu_spa_name">Biwanoyu</string>
    <string name="biwanoyu_spa_hours">9am – 9pm (doors close 8pm)</string>
    <string name="biwanoyu_spa_location">geo:36.266124,137.9891843?q=Biwanoyu</string>
    <string name="biwanoyu_spa_description">Biwa No Yu is an onsen with more than 400 years of history.
        It was founded by the first lord of Matsumoto Castle, Ishikawa, who bathed at the onsen.
        The onsen remained a private area maintained by the palace for many years, and to this day
        is maintained by an ancestor of Lord Ishikawa.</string>
    <string name="hotplaza_spa_name">Hot Plaza Asama</string>
    <string name="hotplaza_spa_hours">10am - 0am (doors close 11pm)</string>
    <string name="hotplaza_spa_location">geo:36.2628454,137.9865075,17z?q=Hot plaza asama onsen</string>
    <string name="hotplaza_spa_description">If you need a wash, this is the place, as it’s the easiest
        to find from the bus station opposite the post office, large uncomplicated. It can get
        a bit busy as it is popular with the gray population as a social locus, but the main pools
        are large you’ll always find a stool to have a wash. Loads of room to sit day dream while
        you wait for the rest of your party  to surface, vending machines massage chairs</string>
    <string name="utsukushigahara_spa_name">Utsukushigahara</string>
    <string name="utsukushigahara_spa_loaction">geo:36.246055,137.9966342,17z?q=白糸の湯</string>
    <string name="utsukushigahara_spa_hours">April - Sept = 6am - 10pm (doors close 9.30pm)\n
        Oct - Mar  = 6.30am - 10pm (doors close 9.30pm)\n
        Weekends/holidays open from 6am
    </string>
    <string name="utsukushigahara_spa_description">Rebuilt fairly recently, this little place caters
        to the local community. As a result it has a regular clientelle can give you ‘local’ feel.
        There’s a sign on the door saying ‘no drunks’ - actually good advice as a hot bath with a
        skinful can seriously damage your health! More of a sento than an onsen, but clean and cheerful,
        as well as cheap. Perhaps best to avoid local ‘rush hour’ - early evening. Your first
        challenge is to decode the vending machine that sells tickets just inside the door -
        tickets which you then hand over to the lady sitting 4 feet away watching you. </string>
    <string name="kaichi_museum_name">Kaichi Gakko Primary School</string>
    <string name="kaichi_museum_hours">8:30am - 4:30pm (doors close 5pm)</string>
    <string name="kaichi_museum_location">geo:36.2430524,137.9660708,17z?q=Kaichi School Museum</string>
    <string name="kaichi_museum_description">One of the oldest elementary schools in Japan. The
        school was completed in 1876 and combines Japan and Western architecture; it operated until
        March 1963. It is a Meiji era cultural site. Various instruction materials and furnishings
        are on display. The school was reconstructed at its current location and restored as a
        museum of education</string>
    <string name="ukiyoe_museum_name">Japan Ukiyo-e Museum</string>
    <string name="ukiyoe_museum_hours">10am - 5pm (doors close 4:30pm)</string>
    <string name="ukiyoe_museum_location">geo:36.2318727,137.9323625,17z?q=Japan Ukiyo-e Museum</string>
    <string name="ukiyoe_museum_descriptions">Japan Ukiyo-e (Ukiyoe) Museum is a print maker\'s dream,
        holding the largest private collection of ukiyo-e (woodblock prints), paintings screens
        and old books in the world. The Sakai family has collected more than 100,000 pieces over
        several generations. English information is limited, but there is a pamphlet you can get at
        the front and the staff are very friendly.</string>
    <string name="art_museum_name">Matsumoto City Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="art_museum_hours">9am - 5pm</string>
    <string name="art_museum_location">geo:36.231628,137.9743083,17z?q=Matsumotoshi Museum</string>
    <string name="art_museum_description">the Matsumoto City Museum of Art\’s four fundamental themes
        are Appreciation, Representation, Learning and Communication. At the entrance is a dynamic
        outdoor installation by Matsumoto native Yayoi Kusama. Her contemporary art takes viewers
        to another world with its almost hallucinatory energy.  The museum features works by other
        Matsumoto artists as well as pieces taking inspiration from the nearby Japanese Alps.</string>
    <string name="timepiece_museum_name">Matsumoto Timepiece Museum</string>
    <string name="timepiece_museum_hours">9am - 5pm (doors close 4:30pm)</string>
    <string name="timepiece_museum_location">geo:36.2337941,137.9664543,17z?q=Matsumotoshi Timepiece Museum</string>
    <string name="timepiece_museum_description">49th year of the Showa era(1974), Mr.Chikazo Honda
        donated his old western and Japanese timepiece collection, in which he devoted himself to,
        hoping many people could enjoy it for a long time. Over the course of time,  some citizens
        donated more timepieces and enriched the collection, which led  to the opening of Matsumoto
        Timepiece Museum on September 1st, 2002. The biggest feature of the museum is that many of
        the timepieces are displayed working.  There are more than 300 timepieces. The museum hopes
        that it will become a landmark in Matsumoto and every visitor has a wonderful time.</string>
</resources>
